# Nikolai Dorofeev

## System Analyst

IT specialist of experience in wide range of technologies. Worked with different ecosystems: JavaScript, Node.js, Python, Java, C#. Integrated systems via REST API, SOAP, gRPC, RabbitMQ. Took lead role in creation of documentation for Kubernetes-based microservices solution.



## Languages

- English: Upper-Intermediate
- Russian: Native

## Skills



UML Microservices

Unix

Security Design patterns

## Work Experience

Full-stack Developer Exactpro (Georgia)

Jul 2022 - Present (1 year 1 month)

- Led development of an easy-to-deploy and easy-to-update docs web toolkit package based on Nuxt.js and Tailwind CSS
- Developed #1 architecture for providing traceability of digital assets between Blockchains for Swift Hackathon 2022
- Mentored junior specialists and technical writers

Full-stack Developer Exactpro

Jul 2021 - Jul 2022 (1 year 1 month)

- Developed a custom website template for documentation with features for technical writers using Gridsome (Vue.js + GraphQL)
- Developed demonstration Python and Kotlin modules for th2 complex Kubernetes-based microservices framework with gRPC and RabbitMQ communication
- Wrote clear and easy-to-understand documentation for complex Kubernetesbased microservices framework

Full-stack Developer International Connections (Freelance)

Feb 2021 - Jul 2021 (6 months)

Developed accounting system for international university connections from scratch:

- Designed PostgreSQL database schema
- Developed REST API with Flask and SQLAlchemy
- Developed Vue.js web client for displaying interactive information with maps integration

Front-end Developer Smart World Academy

Oct 2020 - Dec 2020 (3 months)

Developed web client for an e-learning project similar to Moodle in a team of 2 frontend developers, a backend developer, a system analyst, a UI designer, and a project manager.

Stack: Vue.js, Vuex, Vuetify, SCSS, Axios.

HTML Developer Avatar.xyz (Freelance)

Jun 2020 - Sep 2020 (4 months)

Made e-learning web application adaptive for all screen sizes

Modified Angular components if it was required for layout

### **Projects**

- tradeb0t: in Trading software with high integration possibilities
- <u>th2-cli</u>: 🧖 CLI for managing th2 infrastructure in Kubernetes cluster
- <u>tweetst0rm</u>: Simple app that uses GPT-3 for generating tweets.

### Certificates

- Enterprise Patterns (<u>foxminded.ua</u>, May 2023): Course Page, Certificate, Verify
  Certificate
- Architecting With Google Kubernetes Engine (Coursera, Oct 2021): Certificate
- Fundamentals Of Digital Marketing (<u>Google Digital Garage</u>, Jul 2021):
   Certificate

#### Education

Information Systems And Technologies <u>Tomsk Polytechnic University</u>
Sep 2018 - Jul 2022 (3 years 11 months)

Get a bachelor's degree in Information Systems and Technology in Business.